Guide to the Papers of Abby Weed Grey 1922-1978 MC.151
New York University Archives
- Series XVI: Audiovisual Materials, 57720
  - TV Anchor Channel 2/Grey Reads Poetry., 1975; 57811; 1 sound tape reels TRT: 32:33; Original Label on container: TV Anchor Channel 2; The first 10 minutes of audio cut between broadcast recordings of art auction results and Abby Weed Grey giving information on the broadcasts (dates, networks, locations, etc.); This is followed by 22 minutes of Grey reading poetry; audio quality is poor due to low volume at recording; audio is audible only in the left channel. (Box 30, Reel 7, Box Access 1, Disk 1)
    Scope and Contents
    The first portion is a recording of the St. Paul Minneapolis TV's educational station 2 program. The announcer is discussing six works of art that were donated by the Abby and Ben Grey Foundation. The artwork was part of the Young American Artists group, chosen from the students and faculty at the Minneapolis School of Art and Design. Abby Weed Grey speaks after to explain what TV show this had come from and that it aired on June 5, 1975 at 6:40 pm. The paintings from the Grey Foundation totaled $950. The second portion of this recording is Abby Weed Grey reading poetry. The audio is hard to hear and only comes out of one headphone.
    American poetry -- 20th century.; Broadcasting.; Art.; Art museums -- New York (N.Y.); Art.; Television in education.; Educational television stations.; Art auctions; Auctions in art; Grey, Abby Weed, 1902-1983; Twin Cities Public Television (Saint Paul, Minn.); KTCA-TV (Television station: Saint Paul, Minn.)
  - 1.) Poetry (dip in lake at Bala Nair), Sept. 1963 (?) Poetry reading Pierce and Illinois That's on my 1st talk on art at "U", 57810 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    3" reel 1.5 mil. acetate, 600 ft.
  - Recorder Concert 3/66; Dean Mahyr-May 23, 1966; June 1966 (slip inside), 57809 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    3" reel 1.0 mil. acetate, 900 ft.
  - Bishop Dehqani-St. Matthews, undated; 57808 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    3" reel plastic, 600 ft.
  - 1.) AWG 1971 2.) Abby Weed Grey 1975 re collection & Gallery, 1971, 1975; ref1363; 57807 (Box 30, Folder 11, E-records nyuarchives_MC151, E-records ref1363)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Size: 3" reel
  - 1.) Abby Weed Grey Poetry diary at Deer Lake Aug. 1964 Parviz ( part good) 2.) 1963 (crossed out) (See slip inside), 1963-1964; 57806 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - April 1966-2 cancel-speech (see slip inside for details), 1966 April; 57805 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    3" reel .5 mil mylar, 1200 ft.
  - Peg - May 4, 1966, Sullivan - Fall1965 (see slip), 1965-1966; 57804 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Letter from Parviz to Sia, translated 1/3/65; Sia re: Pakkaz, Pilaram, and Fabrizi letters from Parviz (Sia, Mrs. Grey) Pierce comment re: Artists letter etc. 2/8/65, 1965; 57803 (Box 30, Object 15, Box Access 13, Disk 45, Disk 46)
    3" reel, 2 CDs
  - 1.) Abby Weed Grey & Bishop talk about the possibility of a "garden," how? 2.) Bishop Dehquani talk at Faubault about Sept. 2, 1963 ("A Still Small Voice" & prayer), 1963 September; 57802 (Box 30, Reel 16, Box Access 13, Disk 47, Disk 48)
  - "One World Thru Art"-opening June 16, 1972 Minnesota State Fair grounds gallery Interview with Abby Weed Grey (see slip inside), 1972 June; 57801 (Box 30, Folder 17, Box Digitized Access Files, File mc151_ref1393)
    16mm film, 210 ft, 6 min, 24 fps, Black and White, Sound
  - Deer Lake- Peg Cogswell & Abby Weed Grey conference no. 1, Aug. 29, 1964 (See slip inside with notes), 1964 August; 57800; 1 film reels (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - 1.) Peg re: Bob Luck- April 1965 Paul Schettler- April 29, 1966 Jane & Abby Weed Grey, 1965-1966; 57799; 1 film reels (Box 30, Folder 19)
    1.5 mil. acetate, 600 ft.
  - 1.) cogitations- Pierce diary Deer Lake Aug. 30th 2.) Inventory Deer Lake - "Comm. Thru Art", undated; 57798 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Aug. 1964 Telephone- Peg, Pierce, Paul Shettler, E.L., Pierce (Eldon), 1964 August; 57797 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - -E.L Read Lewis' talk to century club Fall 1965 on Fanny Kemble -copy of recorder concert in Galley Spring 1966, 1965, 1966; MC151_ref1418; 57796; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 22)
    3 1142 04225396 6
  - Abby Weed Grey reading from Gallway Kinnell 8/6/75 report today, 1975 August 6; MC151_ref1423; 57795; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 23)
    1/4 inch open reel audio tape.
  - Parviz, Sia, & Abby Weed Grey - April 1964, 1964 April; MC151_ref1428; 57794; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Pierce re: Janet, Bishop Bayne, Sia re: Parviz, Phillips re: Banking last of July 1966 Recorder one side (see Box 28 Folder 4), MC151_ref1433; 57793; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Abby Weed Grey (side 1 only), undated; MC151_ref1438; 57792; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Mike Milkovich re: exhibit of Contemporary Turkish Painting at MCAD 7/17/71(see Box 28 Folder 5), 1971 July 17; MC151_ref1443; 57791; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - 1.) Abby Weed Grey - talk to "U" writer's group 10/12/64 2.) Parviz re: Prophet April 13, 1963, 1963, 1964; MC151_ref1448; 57790; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Mrs. Grey and Director of Fine Arts from the Smithsonian, undated; MC151_ref1453; 57789; 1 sound tape reels 5:11; Audio quality is good but magnetic hum is audible as is traffic driving around outside where it was being recorded; First minute of audio appears to be Smithsonian director testing microphones. (Box 31, Reel 29, Box Access 1, Disk 2)
    The director of the Fine Arts Collection at the Smithsonian Institution is discussing a new show for India. A woman begins to speak on this show and explains how it was the first time contemporary American Art was in India. Abby Weed Grey is the last to speak and comments on the terrific response to the show in India.
    Existence and Location of Copies note
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 1:2.
    India; Art.; Triennale-India; Grey, Abby Weed, 1902-1983
  - August 12, 1975 CTA thru Jan. 6, 1963, 1963, 1975; MC151_ref1458000001; 57788; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - "Poets and Prophets from Athens to Katmandu"- St. Louis Park Women's Club, "Communication Through Art," New Century Club gallery talk, 1964 January 5-6; MC151_ref1463_000001 and MC151_ref1463_000002; 240586; 1 sound tape reels 51:12; Recording begins at 2:48; Audio speed is slow and irregular but eventually speeds up to normal. All recordings on this tape may be identified by Unique Identifiers beginning with MC151_ref1463. (Box 31, Reel 31, Box Access 1, Disk 3, Disk 4)
    Scope and Contents Note
    Abby Weed Grey is practicing a talk that she will be giving to the St. Louis Park Women's Club on January 5, 1964. Grey is using slides of places that she has been to and of artwork from artists that she has befriended to show how artists are coping with the modern age.
    Religious poetry, Indian; Poetry.; Tibet; Kathmandu (Nepal); India; Kashmir.; Indian poetry; Buddhist poetry, Tibetan; Religious poetry.; Tibetan poetry; Grey, Abby Weed, 1902-1983
  - Nov. 1964 1.) Herstand- conclusion Nov. 11, 1964 re India Art Festival Munzner on ("Genesis-Nov.") Sia Armajani ("Caligraphy") 2.) Peg Cogswell, Steb Bowles, Peg on, MC151_ref1468; 57786; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous 1963 (see Box 28 Folder 6), MC151_ref1473; 57785; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Unidentified, MC151_ref1483_000001; 248846; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Unidentified, undated; MC151_ref1488; 57782; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Unidentified [Abby Weed Grey reading journal/diary?], 1962; MC151_ref1493; 57781; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Unidentified [Christmas Eve], undated; MC151_ref1498; 57780; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Unidentified [Reading Group/Book Club; July 4, 1962], 1962 July 4; MC151_ref1503; 57779; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Unidentified [Flute Playing; Iran], undated; MC151_ref1508; 57778; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Unidentified [Various conversations], undated; MC151_ref1513; 57777; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Unidentified [Various phone conversations], undated; MC151_ref1518; 57776; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - ? Iranian-drums-etc.? (larger reel), undated; MC151_ref1523; 57775; 1 sound tape reels (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Mrs. Grey 1/4 " Master and Transfer (Not on a reel), undated; MC151_ref1528; 57774; 1 sound track film reels (Box 31, Folder 43)
    Appears to be a magnetic soundtrack
  - Writer's Conference #2, 7/17/69 Kinnell, Grey Lecture, 1969 July 17; MC151_ref1533; 57773 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225397 4
    7" reel
  - Grey Memorial Lecture-Writer's Conference 6/15/64, University of Utah Andrew Lytle (slip enclosed), 1964 June 15; MC151_ref1538; 57772 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Bettina Corke's Poet & Philosopher, Final Mix, undated; MC151_ref1543; 57771 (Box 32, Reel 3, Box Access 13, Disk 49)
    7" reel. This tape has been digitized.
  - Lecture in English "American Painting & Sculpture in the U.S." given by Robert M. Gollinpe, undated; MC151_ref1548; 57770 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Iranian Music, undated; MC151_ref1553; 57769 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Summer Writer's Conference #1, 7/17/69 Kinnell-Grey Lecture, 1969 July 17; MC151_ref1558; 57768 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - B.E. Grey Memorial Lecture Mrs. Stanford -Reel 1, undated; MC151_ref1563; 57767 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 1970 Grey Lecture - Reel 1, Part I, MC151_ref1568; 57766 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 1970 Grey Lecture - Reel 2, Part II, MC151_ref1573; 57765 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Lecture in Turkish read by Kerin Ausar for the exhibit on American Painting and sculpture in the U.S., undated; MC151_ref1578; 57764 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Margaret Cornelius' Batiks showing at American Center-Lahore, 1969 January 14; MC151_ref1583; 57763 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Bogata, 6/13/69, 1969 June 13; MC151_ref1588; 57762 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified, undated; MC151_ref1593; 57761 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Footage - Print Minneapolis Young Graphics. Mrs. Grey (in shipping container), undated; MC151_ref1598; 57760; 1 film reels (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Footage - Print Minneapolis Young Graphics. Mrs. Grey (in unmarked shipping container), undated; MC151_ref1603; 57759; 1 film reels (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - WILL (sides 1 & 2), 1977 June 22; MC151_ref1608; 57758; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 1)
    Audio Cassette
  - 1) Set 50 2) Set 51, undated; MC151_ref1613; 57757; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 2)
  - Aug. 20, 1975, 1975 August 20; MC151_1618; 57756; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 3)
  - 1) Ben Dehler 6/9/77 2) Lawrence Boland Sunrise Semester, 1977 June 9; MC151_ref1623; 57755; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 4)
  - Parviz & Slides, undated; MC151_ref1628; 57754; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 5, Box Access 14, Disk 11)
  - 1) Art Purchases from 1st - Thru Clara 2) Paris letters (4/27/76), 1976 April 27; MC151_ref1633; 57753; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 6)
    Audio Cassette. Original housing also included the label "A) Abby: Return from France, 1st Art Purchases - Salt Lake City."
  - Aug. 14, 1975 Interview #2, 1975 August 14; MC151_ref1638; 57752; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 7)
  - Aug. 26, 1975, 1975 August 26; MC151_ref1643_000001 and MC151_ref1643_000002:; 57751; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 8, Box Access 1, Disk 5)
  - Grey Gallery NYU, 1974 December; MC151_ref1648; 57750; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 9)
  - 1) "Fakir" Interview- 1st meeting with Parviz 2) Film: Shiraz Kavir-Lute, undated; MC151_ref1653; 57749; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 10)
  - Aug. 5, 1975 Interview #1, 1975 August 5; MC151_ref1658_000001 and MC151_ref1658_000002; 57748; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 11, Box Access 1, Disk 6)
  - 1) Houses I have lived in 2) 497 Otis home (Not transcribed) 2/3/76, 1976 February 3; MC151_ref1663; 57747; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 12)
  - Deer Lake, 1953 September 18-October 19; MC151_ref1668; 57746; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 13)
  - Description of Deer Lake, 1975 December 7; MC151_ref1673; 57745; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 14)
  - Aug. 19, 1975 Interview #3, 1975 August 19; MC151_ref1678; 57744; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 15)
  - Margaret Cornelius, 1977 June 8; MC151_ref1683; 57743; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 16)
  - 1) "Common Ground" interviews with the Mariers 2) Postman - "radio" 12/29/76, 1976 December 29; MC151_ref1688; 57742; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 17)
  - Abby Weed Grey Interview, 1975 October 6; MC151_ref1693_000001 and MC151_ref1693_000002; 57741; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 18, Box Access 1, Disk 7)
  - Oct. 6, 1975, 2014; MC151_ref1693_000001 and MC151_ref1693_000002; 240594; 1 electronic discs (cd-rom) Track 1: 21:20 Track 2: 31:45
    Existence and Location of Originals Note
    Original cassette tape located in box 12
    Scope Note
    Track 1 Abby Weed Grey is recording herself. She is describing what art means to her and recalls her earliest experiences in art collecting. She reiterates the idea that art can be a form of communication. This recording is easy to hear.
    Track 2 Abby Weed Grey is reading entries from her diary. She begins in 1961 in Isfahan, Persia in which she recalls her time spent there. The recording ends with her reading entries from the later 1960s when she is back in the United States. This recording is easy to hear
  - Early Years thru page 14, undated; MC151_ref1698; 57740; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 19)
  - E.L. on Heline's 1st chapter, 1981 June 1; MC151_ref1703; 57739; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 20)
  - Conversation- St. Paul, MN, Parviz Tanavoli & Abby Weed Grey, 1982 October 9; MC151_ref1708; 57738; 1 sound cassettes (Box 32, Cassette 21)
  - Green And Blue America. Wallace Stevens, undated; MC151_ref1713; 57737; 1 film reels (Box 33, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225398 2
    16mm film reel
  - Pictures at an American Exhibition (First Answer Print), undated; MC151_ref1718; 57736; 1 film reels (Box 33, Folder 2)
    large reel
  - Jamshid Salt Village, 1975, MC151_ref1723; 57735; 1 film reels (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Abby Weed Grey Where?, undated; MC151_ref1728; 57734; 1 film reels (Box 33, Folder 4)
    16 mm film reel
  - Unidentified Reel 1, undated; MC151_ref1733; 57733; 1 film reels (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Orig: High Contract Titles/Credits Iran 1970 A. Wind B. Wind Also Poet/Philosopher, MC151_ref1738; 57732 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    3 small reels in one container.
    Preservation inspection report held at University Archives.
  - Narration-Jacques Poet/Philosopher, Iran 1970, MC151_ref1743; 57731 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Poet/Philosopher, undated; MC151_ref1748; 57730 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Poet/Philosopher, undated; MC151_ref1753; 57729 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    large reel.
  - Poet/Philosopher - Can 3 - Music Trx. A" Effx, undated; MC151_ref1758; 57728 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    2 reels in 2 containers.
  - Poet/Philosopher - Can 4 - Narration Trx. "B" Effx., undated; MC151_ref1763; 57727 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    2 large reels in 2 containers.
  - Poet/Philosopher - Can 6 - Extra Transfer of Narration/Out Takes, undated; MC151_ref1768; 57726 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    12 small reels in two large film containers. Preservation inspection report held at University Archives.
  - Poet/Philosopher - Can 7 - Extra Transfer of Narration and Sound, undated; MC151_ref1773; 57725 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Poet/Philosopher - Can 9 - Pix Outs and Trims, undated; MC151_ref1778; 57724; 1 film reels (Box 33, Folder 14)
    5 small reels in large blue case. Preservation inspection report held at University Archives.
  - Poet/Philosopher - Can 9 - Pix Outs and Trims One over-sized reel-too large for a box entitled Spring in Iran" located under Box 4, in metal reel container, undated; MC151_ref1783; 57723; 1 film reels (Box 34, Folder 15)
    Five small reels contained within one large container.
  - "Spring in Iran", undated; MC151_ref1788; 57722; 1 film reels (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - "Spring in Iran", undated; MC151_ref1793; 57721; 1 film reels (Box 37, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225400 6
  - Poet/Philosopher: The Revival of Bronze Casting in Iran, ca. 1970; MC151_ref2026; 187169; 1 film reels (Box 37, Folder 2, Box Access 13, Disk 51)
    Technical Requirements
    Access copy available.
  - Note enclosed with reel titled "Pierce re: Janet, Bishop Bayne, Sia re: Parviz, Phillips re: Banking last of July 1966 Recorder one side", 248847 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Note enclosed with reel titled "Mike Milkovich re: exhibit of Contemporary Turkish Painting at MCAD 7/17/71", 1971 July 17; 248848 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Notebook- contains notes on contents of reel titled "Miscellaneous 1963" and possibly other reels, undated; 57784 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Multi Media Collection (Box 13B, Box 13C)
- Series XVII: Abby Weed Grey Photographs, 57650
  Scope and Content
  The photographs are housed in 3 manuscript boxes and 2 flat boxes. Inclusive dates are 1962-1982, although the bulk consists of photos from 1965-68.
  - Subseries A: Exhibitions 1962-1972, 57699
    - Communication Thru Art, A.F.A Opening, 1963; 57719 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Dr. Mahmood Ziaii and Dr. Khosrow Behroon, 16 Mar 1963; AWGP_AFA_15_1_1; 227216 (Box 38, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Abby Weed Grey and W. Meader, 16 Mar 1963; AWGP_AFA_15_1_2; 227217 (Box 38, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Abbey Weed Grey, Ms. Barclay, Peggy Barclay, Mrs. Leach, 16 Mar 1963; AWGP_AFA_15_1_2; 227219 (Box 38, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Mr. Arnold, Abby Weed Grey, Mr. Counsel, 16 Mar 1963; AWGP_AFA_15_1_4; 227220 (Box 38, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Mr. Arnold and Abbey Weed Grey, 16 Mar 1963; AWGP_AFA_15_1_5; 227221 (Box 38, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Students at showing at Fine Arts Academy, 13 Jan 1964; AWGP_AFA_15_1_6; 227222 (Box 38, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Communication Thru Art, Lahore, Pakistan, 1964; 57718 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      3 1142 04225401 4
      - Seminar at the "Communication Through Art" Art Week, 1964; AWGP_CAP_15_2_1; 227223 (Box 38, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Visitors Viewing the Art At the Exhibit, 1964; AWGP_CAP_15_2_2; 227224 (Box 38, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Mt Malik Shams of the Pakistan Arts Council discusses a point with Mr. Justice S.A. Rahman., 1964; AWGP_CAP_15_2_3; 227225 (Box 38, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Mr Saeed Ahmad and Professor John Ferren Meet Before the "Communication Through Art Exhibit", 1964; AWGP_CAP_15_2_4; 227226 (Box 38, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Discussion Panel at the "Communication Through Art" Exhibit, 1964; AWGP_CAP_15_2_5; 227227 (Box 38, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - An Interested Group of Art-Minded Viewers Attend the Exhibit, 1964; AWGP_CAP_15_2_6; 227228 (Box 38, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Opening of "Communication Through Art" in a Shamiana, 1964; AWGP_CAP_15_2_7; 227229 (Box 38, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Turkish Art Today, Opening Installation, 1965; 57717 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Two Women at The Opening Installation, 1965; AWGP_TOA_15_3_1; 227230 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Man Sitting at the Opening Installation, 1965; AWGP_TOA_15_3_2; 227231 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Two Men Sitting at the Opening Installation, 1965; AWGP_TAO_15_3_3; 227232 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Woman at the Opening Installation, 1965; AWGP_TOA_15_3_4; 227233 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Man Standing at the Opening Installation, 1965; AWGP_TOA_15_3_5; 227234 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Exhibit Audience Member, 1965; AGWP_TAO_15_3_6; 227235 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Mustafa Aslier at Opening Installation, 1965; AGWP_TAO_15_37; 227236 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Man Smoking a Pipe at the Opening Installation, 1965; AGWP_TAO_15_3_8; 227237 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Exhibit Audience Member, 1965; AGWP_TAO_15_3_9; 227238 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Man Smoking a Cigarette at the Opening Installation, 1965; AWGP_TAO_15_3_10; 227239 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Man in Glasses at the Opening Installation, 1965; AWGP_TAO_15_3_11; 227240 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Woman in the Kitchen at the Opening Installation, 1965; AGWP_TAO_15_3_12; 227241 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Exhibit Audience at the Opening Installation, 1965; AWGP_TAO15_3_13; 227242 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Grey Foundation Turkish Show Opening in USIS Istanbul, 1966; AGWP_TAO_15_3_14; 227243 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 14)
      - Mrs. Benjamin Grey, left, joined Mrs. Patrick Butler and Mr. Conrad Hanson at the Exhbit of Contemporary Turkish Art on Display in the First National Bank of St. Paul, 1967; AGWP_TAO_15_3_15; 227244 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 15)
      - Visitors Gathered Around a Work of Art at the Opening Installation, 1965; AGWP_TAO_15_3_16; 227245 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 16)
      - J. Turami in Ankara, Turkey, 1964; AGWP_TAO_15_3_17; 227246 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 17)
      - TAA Fine Arts Group in Ankara, Turkey, 1964; AGWP_TAO_15_3_18; 227247 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 18)
      - Visitors Viewing Three of the Turkisk Works of Art, 1965; AGWP_TAO_15_3_19; 227248 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 19)
      - Exhibit Audience Members, 1965; AGWP_TAO_15_3_20; 227249 (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 20)
    - National College of Arts Gift, Pakistan, 1966; 57716 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Man with art projects in terrace, 1966; AWGP_NCP_15_4_1; 227338 (Box 38, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Mr. Akhtar and Students of National College of Arts, December 1966; AWGP_NCP_15_4_2; 227339 (Box 38, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Robert Jones, USIS Lahore, Shakir Ali, Mrs. Abbasi Akhtar, December 1966; AWGP_NCP_15_4_3; 227340 (Box 38, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Robert Jones addressing faculty and students, December 1966; AWGP_NCP_15_4_4; 227341 (Box 38, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - American Prints Exhibit, Iran-American Society Building Opening, 1967; 57715 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - American Prints Exhibit Audience, 1966; AWGP_AFA_15_5_1; 227345 (Box 38, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Letter to Abby Grey From Collin Ostrander Regarding photos, April 26, 1966; AWGP_AFA_15_5_2; 227346 (Box 38, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Mr. Hassan Ali Sedqi-Vaziri and other government officials at exhibit., 1966; AWGP_AFA_15_5_3; 227347 (Box 38, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - University of Tehran Foundry, Students Exhibit, undated; 57714 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Student Art Studio, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_1; 227353 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Student Art Studio, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_2; 227354 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Her Imperial Empress Farah shakes hands with Abby Weed Grey, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_3; 227355 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Her Imperial Empress Farah with Abby Weed Grey, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_4; 227358 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Exhibit Audience and Her Imperial Empress Farah, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_5; 227359 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Exhibit Audience at Opening, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_6; 227367 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Her Imperial Empress Farah and Abbey Weed Grey, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_7; 227368 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Her Imperial Empress Farah Arrival, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_8; 227369 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Abby Weed Grey at Exhibit Opening, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_9; 227370 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Exhibit Talk with Abbey Weed Grey, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_10; 227371 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Exhibit Audience, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_11; 227388 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Exhibit Audience Looks at Art on Table, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_12; 227394 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 12)
      - Student Artist in Studio Talks to Audience, AWGB_UTE_15_6_13; 227395 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 13)
      - Students and Audience in Studio, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_14; 227396 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 14)
      - Art Studio Terrace Outdoors, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_15; 227397 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 15)